<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MinuteMedia product and tech blog on MinuteMedia Tech and Product Blog</title>
    <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MinuteMedia product and tech blog on MinuteMedia Tech and Product Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MinuteMedia - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:42:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tech.minutemedia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Ducks vs. Static Gophers</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/dynamic-ducks-vs-static-gophers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/dynamic-ducks-vs-static-gophers/</guid>
      <description>Until recently, I have professionally worked only with Ruby and Javascript. It’s only been about three years since I got my first programming job. I used these languages because that’s what the code was already written in, as it is with most of the starting web companies out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scale or Fail: The Story Behind Minute Media’s Editor Redesign</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/scale-or-fail-the-story-behind-minute-medias-editor-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/scale-or-fail-the-story-behind-minute-medias-editor-redesign/</guid>
      <description>Scale or Fail: The Story Behind Minute Media’s Editor Redesign In 2015, Minute Media released its Editor to more than 200 writers and 20 content managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soft Landing in A New Job</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/soft-landing-in-a-new-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/soft-landing-in-a-new-job/</guid>
      <description>The first thing I found out in 2019 was, that starting a new job as a senior developer was surprisingly difficult. The interviews are one thing, but when your first day finally arrives and you march in there wearing your senior developer hat, then it’s time to put your money where your mouth is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Mars! A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Hi-tech</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/welcome-to-mars-a-beginners-guide-to-hi-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/welcome-to-mars-a-beginners-guide-to-hi-tech/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Mars! A Beginners Guide to Hi-tech
So, you got accepted to your dream job in a successful startup company. You passed about 6 interviews, a home assignment (in my case a design assignment), you signed an 11 page contract (in English of course) and now you are about to start working&amp;hellip;but wait - do you know what you are actually getting yourself in to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Chapter to Making Your Pods Successful</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/the-lost-chapter-to-making-your-pods-successful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 15:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/the-lost-chapter-to-making-your-pods-successful/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;#39;ve reached the stage of exploring the option of utilizing the pod structure or maybe you&amp;#39;ve already started it. You&amp;#39;ve reviewed the different guides which talk about processes, structure and efficiency, everything sounds great but you feel like something is missing&amp;hellip; You are right, there is a missing chapter which relates to the human aspect and the effect moving to pods has on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Using a Monorepo is Helping Us Work Better</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/how-monorepo-is-helping-us-work-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/how-monorepo-is-helping-us-work-better/</guid>
      <description>As any other mature startup moving to its growth stage, Minute Media had to rebuild its infrastructure.
Our initial infrastructure was a Monolithic application in Ruby on Rails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reporting Errors in Production: The Type/Stack Conflict</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/reporting-errors-in-production-the-type-stack-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 16:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/reporting-errors-in-production-the-type-stack-conflict/</guid>
      <description>Lately, my team and I started reporting errors to Sentry. I hate to admit it, but only then did I notice that my errors aren’t telling me much at a glance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY: Creating a Great Relationship Between Dev &amp; Design</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/diy-creating-a-great-relationship-between-dev-and-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 15:25:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/diy-creating-a-great-relationship-between-dev-and-design/</guid>
      <description>A successful relationship between dev &amp;amp; design is key to achieving a good product. However, unfortunately in most places it is not the case. Today in Minute Media, designers and developers are working together in a good and healthy atmosphere - but it took a lot of work to get to this point, and it takes constant work to maintain it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>