<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video on Minute Media Tech and Product Blog</title>
    <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video on Minute Media Tech and Product Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Minute Media - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 12:12:12 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tech.minutemedia.com/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefit From Minute Media’s Impressive Video Content Library</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/benefit-from-minute-medias-impressive-video-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 12:12:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/benefit-from-minute-medias-impressive-video-library/</guid>
      <description>With so many options available to the end user today, the need for relevant and engaging video content is more important than ever. If publishers want to be successful in leveraging and monetizing video as a part of their offering, they will need the right content to help them achieve these goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Increasing User Engagement With Minute Media&#39;s Video Content Recirculation Tool</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/inscreasing-user-engagement-with-minute-medias-video-content-recirculation-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 12:12:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/inscreasing-user-engagement-with-minute-medias-video-content-recirculation-tool/</guid>
      <description>To provide users with the best possible video experience, publishers need access to relevant and engaging content. Our fully automated video recirculation tool allows publishing partners to boost their content offering, increase time spent on page and drive more revenue by converting existing stories into engaging videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 - How We&#39;re Trying to Stir Through This Unprecedented Crisis and Help Our Partners Along the Way</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/covid19-how-were-trying-to-stir-through-this-unprecedented-crisis-and-help-our-partners-along-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 12:12:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/covid19-how-were-trying-to-stir-through-this-unprecedented-crisis-and-help-our-partners-along-the-way/</guid>
      <description>Dear Partners,
The coronavirus pandemic has changed the world in ways we couldn’t have ever imagined. While things are changing every few days, the challenges the media industry will be facing in the coming months are becoming more and more apparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Minute Media&#39;s Matching Algorithm Helps Publishers Take Their Video Offering to The Next Level</title>
      <link>https://tech.minutemedia.com/how-minute-medias-matching-algorithm-helps-publishers-take-their-video-offering-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 12:12:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.minutemedia.com/how-minute-medias-matching-algorithm-helps-publishers-take-their-video-offering-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>My father always orders the same ice cream. ‘One cone with vanilla and chocolate, please’ - I must have heard him say this sentence a thousand times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>